(self.webpackChunk_N_E=self.webpackChunk_N_E||[]).push([[892],{6383:function(e,t,o){(window.__NEXT_P=window.__NEXT_P||[]).push(["/bettercanvas/questions",function(){return o(5305)}])},5305:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);var n=o(5893),s=o(1163);t.default=()=>{let e=e=>{let{problem:t,solution:o,highlight:i}=e,r=(0,s.useRouter)(),a=r.query.highlight===i,h=a?{}:{highlight:i};return(0,n.jsxs)("div",{style:{cursor:"pointer"},onClick:()=>r.push({pathname:"",query:h}),children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"space-between",background:a?"#141414":"none",padding:"20px",borderRadius:"10px"},children:[(0,n.jsx)("p",{style:{fontSize:"22px",fontWeight:"500"},children:t}),(0,n.jsxs)("svg",{style:{transform:"rotate(".concat(a?180:0,"deg)"),transition:".25s transform"},xmlns:"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg",width:"24",height:"24",viewBox:"0 0 24 24",fill:"none",stroke:"currentColor","stroke-width":"2","stroke-linecap":"round","stroke-linejoin":"round",children:[(0,n.jsx)("path",{stroke:"none",d:"M0 0h24v24H0z",fill:"none"}),(0,n.jsx)("path",{d:"M6 9l6 6l6 -6"})]})]}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{style:{display:a?"block":"none",color:"#b5b5b5",fontSize:"18px",marginLeft:"20px",marginTop:"10px"},children:o})]})};return(0,n.jsx)("div",{style:{minHeight:"100vh",background:"#0a0a0c",display:"flex",justifyContent:"center"},children:(0,n.jsxs)("div",{style:{maxWidth:"1100px",width:"100%",color:"#fff",margin:"120px 0"},children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,n.jsx)("h1",{style:{fontSize:"34px",fontWeight:"bold"},children:"Frequent issues"}),(0,n.jsx)("p",{style:{color:"#b5b5b5",marginTop:"5px"},children:"Here's some answers!"})]}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{style:{background:"linear-gradient(115deg, #ff3558, #ff8349, #ff67bb)",height:"4px",width:"100%",marginTop:"20px",borderRadius:"100px"}}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",gap:"60px",flexWrap:"wrap"},children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{style:{flex:"1",marginTop:"15px",display:"flex",flexDirection:"column",gap:"10px"},children:[(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"0",problem:"Canva",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"This extension is NOT for Canva the graphic design tool. It will not work with Canva."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"11",problem:"D2L/Moodle/Ultra/non-canvas users",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"This extension does NOT work with these learning platforms. They use entirely different systems so they are not compatible."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"12",problem:"Resetting on refresh",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"Please check if you have turned on scheduled dark mode instead of the regular dark mode. The extension might not be resetting, it could just be automatically turning off the dark mode because you have this option on."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"1",problem:"Nothing happens",solution:(0,n.jsxs)("p",{children:["Here are a few things to check for:",(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),"- Better Canvas only works with Canvas, so if you're trying to use any other platform it won't work.",(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),"- Make sure the url in the menu is set and is the same url you see when on your Canvas dashboard.",(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),"- Make sure the dashboard is in card view and not list view, since most of the features only work in card view."]})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"3",problem:"Fix dark mode gaps",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"It can be hard to target everything because gaps need to be manually fixed and I don't have access to some places that you may have. In the Edit Dark Mode tab, you will find a dark mode fixer option which you can try running on the page. If this doesn't fix the gap, please send an email to ksucpea@gmail.com so I can get more details to fix the issue."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"9",problem:"Support for Safari, Edge, and others",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"The only supported browsers are Chrome and Firefox. I don't have a Mac so I am unable to port the extension to Safari at this time. Additionally, the Edge addon store does not work, so I can't support the extension on there either. There are no plans to support other browsers such as Opera."})})]}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{style:{flex:"1",marginTop:"15px",display:"flex",flexDirection:"column",gap:"10px"},children:[(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"4",problem:"Missing cards or cards not found error",solution:(0,n.jsxs)("p",{children:["If you're trying to use this extension for anything other than Canvas (i.e. D2L, Moodle, Ultra, Blackboard) or the graphic design tool Canva, the extension will not work. It is not compatible with these platforms.",(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),"Otherwise, go to the Report Issue tab in the Better Canvas menu, scroll down to Card Method, and click Dashboard. This will tell the extension to try and retrieve your cards in a different way. Please note that this is still an experimental feature and some features may be broken as a result (for example the GPA calculator) but I am working on a fix."]})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"2",problem:"Creating a theme",solution:(0,n.jsxs)("p",{children:["To make a theme you'll need to put in images for your cards, customize the dark mode, select cards colors, select a custom font, etc. You don't have to do all of these, but I only accept themes with at least a dark mode and card images. You can see examples of themes in the User Made Themes section in the menu. I also no longer accept themes that use one of the default dark mode presets, so please make sure your dark mode is unique. ",(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),(0,n.jsx)("br",{})," Once your theme is ready, you can then export it by going to the export section under the themes tab. Then, select the checkboxes to generate an output that you can send to my email, ksucpea@gmail.com. ",(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),(0,n.jsx)("br",{}),"Be sure to include the name of your theme and your name for credit! (this can be anything - your real name, handle, anonymous etc.)"]})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"5",problem:"Card colors not working",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"Make sure you're on the dashboard page and the dashboard is in card view. You may also need to have only one Canvas page open."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"6",problem:"Changing card colors",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"If you are not happy with your card colors, you can click on the three dots in the top right corner of each card to change their color individually."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"7",problem:"Card colors becoming muted",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"You likely have High Contrast UI enabled. You can change this by clicking on your account icon in the sidebar and disabling the setting there."})}),(0,n.jsx)(e,{highlight:"8",problem:"Why was my theme not added",solution:(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"I appreciate you taking the time to submit your theme, however due to the number of submissions I receive, I try to add only high quality themes that are complete. If your theme is missing compenents (i.e. dark mode, card images), uses one of the default dark modes, or is too similar to another theme, then this is likely why I couldn't add it."})})]})]})]})})}},1163:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o(6885)}},function(e){e.O(0,[774,888,179],function(){return e(e.s=6383)}),_N_E=e.O()}]);